24小时
第三季  第9集
前情提要
今天所发生的一切 从医疗中心的感染尸体
Sir, everything that's happened today from the infected body at Health Services
到拉姆·萨拉扎的越狱都属于一次精心策划的苦肉计
through Ramon Salazar's prison break has been a part of an elaborate sting operation.
总统先生
Mr. President,
一小撮乌克兰的科学正试图在黑市上销售一种武器化病毒
a group of scientists from the Ukraine were trying to sell a weaponized virus on the open market
我而我推荐了萨拉扎组织
and I suggested the Salazars as potential buyers.
我们的目的是在市场上根除货源
Our goal was to remove the virus stock pile from the marketplace.
成败的先决条件是
But all of this hinged on me convincing the Salazars
让萨拉扎兄弟我已经叛变了
that I had switched sides.
告诉我 这叛徒怎么会成了我们朋友
Tell me how the man who betrayed us is now our friend.
鲍尔给我送来一个机会
Bauer came to me with an opportunity
能挣很多钱
to make more money
多到我们无法想象
than we have ever dreamed of.
这对你有什么好处 杰克?
What's in it for you, Jack?
1千5百万美金
$15 million.
我从来没想过杰克·鲍尔会为钱干事
I would never have thought that Jack Bauer was for sale.
你说过你会带我离开这里
You said you'd take me away from here.
还记得么 杰克?
Do you remember, Jack?
是的 我还记得
Yes, I remember.
其实你只有一件事没有明说...
There was one small thing you forgot to mention.
你是个警察
You are a cop.
但是我不在乎这 只要你还能记住一丁点承诺
But even that wouldn't matter if you'd meant half the things you said to me
我对你所说的话 都是真心诚意的
I meant everything I ever said to you.
往后的几小时里
For the next few hours,
我们要倾尽一切资源帮助杰克·鲍尔阻截病毒
all of our resources are dedicated to helping Jack Bauer intercept this virus.
托尼 我和蔡斯通过话
Tony, I spoke to Chase.
他不会回到反恐局
He's not coming back to CTU.
蔡斯依旧认为我父亲是被萨拉扎他们绑架了
He still thinks my father was captured by the Salazars.
因此他要前往拯救杰克.
And he thinks he's going in to rescue Jack.
该死的! 如果他一去 杰克的身份就暴露了
Damn it. If he goes in there, he's going to blow Jack's cover.
那我们就拿不到病毒了
We're going to lose this virus.
我认识他
I know this man.
他是鲍尔的搭档
Bauer's partner!
这到底是怎么回事 杰克?
What the hell's going on here, Jack?
闭嘴 蔡斯!
Shut up, Chase!
你根本不该跟踪我
You should never have followed me down here.
-你和他们一伙了?  -没错
-You with them?  -Yes, I'm with them.
-杰克  -闭嘴 蔡斯!
-Jack.  -Shut up, Chase.
你如果还想活命 就给我闭嘴!
You want to get through this, just shut up!
杰克的手表发信器坏了
The transponder in Jack's watch just went dead.
该死的!
Damn it!
即使突击部队就位
By the time the assault teams are in position,
我们也根本不知道他身在何处
we'll have no idea where he is.
女士们先生们 总统将会宣布简短公告
Ladies And Gentlemen, the President will make a brief statement.
不设提问
There will be no questions at this time.
我亲爱的美国人民 晚上好
My fellow americans, good evening.
几小时前
A few hours ago,
我不得不中止 总统竞选辩论
I had to terminate the presidential debate
来处理手头要事
in order to handle what was at the time
一项国家安全问题
a national security threat.
我目前无法向你们透露
I can't reveal to you at this time
情况的细节
for the details surrounding the situation.
几小时后 一切都将水落石出
Those will be forthcoming in the next few hours.
但我保证几小时前的危机已经不复存在
Let me assure you that the danger that existed a few hours ago has passed.
美国安全了
America is safe,
美国人民也安全了
the American people are safe.
我向我的竞选对手 参议员基勒以及
I apologize to my opponent, Senator Keeler,
期待看到我们辩论的上百万民众表示歉意
and to the millions of you who were expecting to see the two of us engaged in the issues.
辩论将择日再举行
The debate will be rescheduled.
我向各位的耐心及宽容表示谢意
I'd like to thank you all for your patience and understanding.
-晚安  -总统先生
-Good night.  -Mr. Prident, Mr. President,
有流言说此次危机是由您的官员所捏造
there have been rumors that this crisis was manufactured by your administration
意图袒护您的朋友 安妮 帕卡德医生
to protect your friend, Dr. Anne Packard.
您对此怎么看?
How do you respond to that, sir?
这些传言是捏造的
Those allegations were false.
参议员基勒的指控是空穴来风 我们有证据
Senator Keeler's charges were unfounded and we have proof.
由安妮 帕卡德的前夫所提供
Proof that comes directly from Anne Packard's ex-husband.
事实上 之后一段时间里
In fact, in the next few days and weeks,
参议员基勒得想法自圆其说
Senator Keeler will have his own explaining to do.
安妮 帕卡德是一个正直善良的人
Anne Packard is an individual of the utmost integrity.
她不应受到如此待遇
She didn't deserve this.
总统先生!
Mr. President!
谢谢 女士们先生们
Thank you. Thank you, Ladies and Gentlemen.
到此为止 提问结束 谢谢
That's it. No more questions. Thank you.
鲍尔和萨拉扎兄弟在墨西哥
Bauer's with the Salazar brothers in Mexico.
他的跟踪器失灵了
His transponder signal has stopped working.
我们要竭尽所能联系上他
We're doing everything we can to reestablish contact.
让特种部队在收到我消息前 原地待命
Tell the Delta units to hold their positions till I get back to you.
对 谢谢
Right. Thanks.
为什么我们不试试增幅器?
Why don't we try an amplification module?
我已经试了3次了
I've already cycled through it three times.
不是信号薄弱 而是根本没有
It's not a weak signal, there's no signal.
我们觉得有哪些可能性?
What do we think happened here?
很有可能杰克的身份被揭穿了
There's a strong possibility that Jack's cover might have been blown.
没有任何征兆说明他的跟踪器被发现
There's no indication that his transponder's been found
或者他的身份败露
or that his cover's been blown.
有可能他所在的地方发不出信号
It may be either he's in a place where we can't get the signal
或者他的跟踪器坏了
or the transponder's broken.
部分受损可能会改变其原有频率
Partial damage might have knocked it to another frequency.
-扫描一下频带  -我正在干
-Let's run a scan.  -I'm doing that now.
到现在为止只查了三分之一 但是到目前为止没有找到
I'm only a third of the way through the spectrum, but so far, no luck.
好吧 我会找人帮你
All right, I'll get you some help.
金.
Kim
-怎么 托尼?  -你知道怎么进行频带扫描么?
-Yes, Tony?  -Do you know how to do a frequency scan?
知道
Yeah.
好吧 我们试图搜索你父亲的跟踪器信号
Okay. We're trying to pick up your father's transponder signal.
米歇尔已经在搜索了 配合她
Michelle's already begun the scan. Coordinate with her.
-署名是什么?  -我已经说过了30/5
-What's the signature?  -I already told you... 30 over five.
你没说过
You didn't tell me.
听着 金
Look, Kim.
我知道你不好过
I know it's hard on you...
你父亲生死未卜
your father's life being at stake...
但是你得集中注意力 明白?
but I need you to focus, okay?
抱歉
Sorry.
就这样
All right, good.
如果有什么消息 告诉我
Call me if anything changes.
为什么我们停在这儿?
Why are we stopped?
托马斯说我们没被跟踪
Tomas says there is no sign of anyone following us.
在我们了解到更多前 我们最好呆在这儿
Until we know more, we're better off staying here.
他会不会是孤身前来?
Would he have come here on his own without backup?
也许他想独自救你
Maybe he came by himself to rescue you.
太可怜了
How sad.
你难过么 杰克 你搭档因为救你而死?
Does it bother you, Jack, that your partner's going to die, trying to save you?
很难过
It breaks me up.
然后灭口
Then kill him.
那个叫阿马多尔的 应该已经打电话安排会面了
This man Amador should have called by now to set up the meeting.
他会联系的 别担心
He's going to call, don't worry.
只要你准备好钱
Just make sure you got your money ready.
钱已经准备好了
The money's ready.
喂?
Yeah?
我是阿马多尔
It's Amador.
我们准备好了
We're ready.
哪儿见?
Where?
让鲍尔接电话
Put Bauer on the phone.
我只和他谈
I only deal with him.
我是杰克
This is Jack.
杰克 小镇北面5公里处 有通往丛林的岔道
Hi, Jack. Five kilometers north of the town, the trail splits off the road into the woods.
沿着那条路2公里 15分钟路程
Take the two kilometers. 15 minutes.
明白
Got it.
接头点在这里北面 15分钟内赶到
The meeting's north of here in 15 minutes.
等下
Wait.
给我电话
The phone.
如果他打回来呢?
What if he calls back?
我会留言
I'll take a message.
看看你 杰克 你看起来糟透了
Look at you, Jack. You are a mess.
我们得帮你收拾干净 不然你肯定挺不过去
We got to get you straight or you'll never get through this.
我不使用毒品
I'm not gonna fix.
吃点这个
Take them.
你会好些
You'll feel better.
我得用下厕所
I need to use the bathroom.
里面就是
They're in the back.
我希望你睡会
I want you to get some sleep.
-我不累  -走的时候 我会叫醒你的
-I'm not tired.  -I'll wake you when it's time to leave.
-赫克托呢?  -他很忙
-Where's Hector?  -He's busy.
明天早上你就能看到他
You'll see him tomorrow morning.
睡吧
Go to sleep.
我爱你
I love you.
克劳迪娅 坐下!
Claudia, sit down!
坐下!
Sit down!
我要你仔细听我说
I need you to listen to me.
赫克托和拉姆要购买细菌武器
Hector and Ramon are trying to buy a virus to use as a weapon.
上百万人会因此死去
Millions of people could die.
我安排这场交易 帮助美国政府控制病毒并消灭它
I've set up this deal so my government can take control of the virus and destroy it.
你明白我在说什么?
Do you understand what I'm saying?
你还在为反恐局干?
You're still with CTU?
是的 我还是属于反恐局的
Yes, I'm still with CTU.
但是你帮拉姆越狱了
But you broke Ramon out of prison.
这样我才能得到他的信任
That was so I could gain his trust,
来进行这场交易
to make the deal happen.
我不能让病毒落入魔掌
I cannot allow this virus to get into the wrong hands.
你骗了我们一次 现在你又要欺骗我们?
You betrayed us once, now you've come to betray us again?
是骗他们 不是骗你
No, it's them, not you.
我像一个笨蛋一样轻信
I was a fool to believe any of it.
我会保护你 并把你家人送到安全地带
I'm going to protect you and going to get your family somewhere safe.
-撒谎  -我很早就想回来找你
-All lies.  -I wanted to come back for you earlier,
但是当我听到病毒问题 我得优先处理这个
but when I heard about this virus, I had to deal with it.
几百万人性命攸关 你得明白这点
Millions of lives are at stake. You have to understand that.
这次我可以把你带出去
But I can get you out now.
你 塞尔吉奥和你父亲
You, Sergio and your father.
-怎么做?  -美国士兵离这儿不远
-How?  -American soldiers are not far from here.
他们在等我消息 但是我联系不到他们
They're waiting for my signal, but I can't reach them
因为我的跟踪器坏了
because my transmitter's been destroyed.
克劳迪娅
Claudia,
骗你对我没有好处
I have nothing to gain from telling you this if it's not the truth.
只要你一句话 我就死路一条
One word from you and I'm a dead man.
你要我做什么?
What do you want me to do?
首先 我需要手机 我得和反恐局联系 报告我的位置
First, I need a cell phone. I need to let CTU know where I am.
然后 我要你尽量
Then I need you to do whatever you can
帮助我的搭档 蔡斯
to help my partner Chase,
-让他活着  -不行 赫克托一旦发现
-to keep him alive.  -No, when Hector realizes it,
-我就活不了了  -那时我们早就远走高飞了
-he's going to kill me.  -We'll be gone by then.
蔡斯可以帮你逃出去
Chase can help you get out,
我保证
I promise.
但是如果我联系不上反恐局 这一切就都完了
But if I can't contact CTU, this is all for nothing.
你得给我电话
You've got to get me that phone.
求你了
Please.
我会尽力的
I'll do what I can.
我得走了 他们正等着我
I have to go. They're waiting for me.
如果你再骗我
If you're lying to me again,
我就亲手杀了你
I'll kill you myself.
去救蔡斯
Help Chase.
杰克·鲍尔帮拉姆越狱
Jack Bauer broke Ramon out of prison.
你们的人会来抓他们
Your people are sending forces to bring them back.
他们什么时候来?
When are they coming?
时间?
When?
地点?
and where?
动手
quiere mas.
他原本是你搭档
He was your partner.
你心情一定不好受
You must be feeling something.
我能从这笔交易里分到1千5百万美金
I've got a $15 million payday when this deal goes down.
因此我帮不了他
He's on his own.
他和你一样倔强么?
Is he as tough as you?
他依旧生活在谎言中
He still believes in the lie.
什么谎言?
What lie?
他认为自己的所作所为是有意义的
That what he's doing has purpose.
有信仰是好事
Belief is a beautiful thing.
嗨
Hello.
你去哪儿?
Where are you going?
-别这样  -不嘛...
-Please.  -Don't...
拉姆在等我
Ramon is waiting, okay?
克劳迪娅?
Claudia?
我把手机忘里面了
I left my phone inside.
我会去取的
I'll get it.
我们走
Let's go.
-克萝伊  -怎么?
-Chloe.  -What?
-有蔡斯的消息么?  -没有
-Have you heard from Chase?  -No.
他有没有可能 用其它频率联系你
Are there alternate frequencies he might use to contact you?
有 那些频道正在扫描中
Yeah, there are, and they're on auto-scan.
-他没有联系  -听我说 克萝伊 我知道你很忙
-He hasn't checked in.  -Look, Chloe, I know that you're busy,
但是我们也许可以通过卫星找到他
but maybe we can reach him by satellite.
卫星? 好主意 我怎么没想到呢 金
Satellite? Good idea. I didn't i think of that, Kim.
-我马上去弄  -你没必要冷嘲热讽 克萝伊
-I'll get right on that.  -Don't be sarcastic with me, Chloe.
我只是关心他们
This is someone I care about.
放轻松
Get a grip.
半小时内我得给总统报告
I have to update the President in half an hour.
我不想告诉他半小时内我们毫无进展 毫无头绪
I don't want to tell him we're in the same place we were a half-hour ago, which is nowhere.
我不想听借口 我只要答案 明白?
I don't want excuses. Just get me the answer, all right?
我得完成通讯文件
I need to finalize the comm file.
你应该已经完成了
That should have been done already.
我需要格式码 你说你会去下载的
Well, I need the format code and you said you were going to download it.
d-7-3-3-g
Delta-seven-three-three-golf.
这是前一份文件的
That's the code from the previous file.
d-7-2-3-b
Delta-seven-two-three-bravo.
-谢谢  -没事
-Thank you.  -All right.
你拿到了么?
Did you get it?
拿到了
Yeah, I got it.
密码错误 会浪费8分钟
Eight minutes shot to hell on an invalid code.
进去了
Access granted.
如果错了结果会很严重 少了那些文件
That could have been a disaster. Without those files,
我们联系不上救援队
we can't track the rescue teams.
进来
Come.
坏消息 反恐局失去了杰克·鲍尔的信号
Bad news. CTU lost track of Jack Bauer.
-他有麻烦了?  -我们不知道
-Is he in trouble?  -We don't know.
他得到病毒了?
Does he have possession of the virus yet?
我们也不知道 大卫
We don't know that, either, David.
进来
Come.
总统先生 艾伦·米利肯在线上等你
Mr. President, I have Alan Milliken on the line for you.
我来接
I'll take it.
-艾伦?  -大卫?
-Alan?  -David?
你生我气么?
You angry with me?
当然不
Of course I'm not angry with you.
三年里你第一次来洛杉矶
Your first time in L.A. in three years and
连个电话都没打
you don't even call.
今天不是个好日子 艾伦
It's been a bad day, Alan.
我知道 我看过新闻了
I know. I've been watching the news.
我不想增加你的负担 但还是想过来拜访你
I don't want to add to your burdens, but I'd like to come by and see you.
拜访我?
See me?
大卫
David.
如果不是要事 我不会来找你
I wouldn't ask if it weren't important.
我知道你很忙
I know you're busy.
你毕竟是美国总统
After all, you are the President of the United States.
这大部分归功于你
In large part, thanks to you.
我来找你 艾伦
I'll come to you, Alan.
15分钟内 我会到
I'll be there in 15 minutes.
谢谢 大卫
Thank you, David.
还有一件事
And one more thing.
作为个人要求
As a personal favor to me,
我不想让韦恩一起来
I'm asking you not to bring Wayne.
我能询问理由么?
May I ask why?
我想面对面和你解释
That's something I'd rather explain in person.
好吧
All right.
-进行得怎么样?  -到目前为止
-Where are we?  -So far,
还是联系不上杰克
we're not able to pick up Jack on any of our imagery.
我们失去联系有多久了?
How long we been out of contact?
从他的跟踪器失灵开始...
His tracking beacon went dead...
有27分钟了
27 minutes ago.
最后的位置?
Last known location?
这儿
Here.
他一定在这方圆30英里内
He can't be much farther out than 30 miles in any one direction.
除非他被直升机送走
Unless he was choppered out.
不可能 空军一直监视着空域
No way. Air tactical's watching the skies.
鲍尔在哪儿?
Where's Bauer?
我们不知道
We don't know yet.
好极了
That's great.
那么
So,
这个以杰克在病毒交易现场
this entire operation, which hinges on Jack being on-site
为先决条件的行动即将功亏一篑
when they deliver the virus, is going down the tubes
因为我们不知道他身在何处
because we don't know where he is.
-怎么会变得这样?  -听着 瑞恩
-How does that happen?  -Look, Ryan,
你想要骂我们?
you want to chew us out?
晚点可以 现在我们得努力把一切搞定
Do it later. We're trying to get this back on track.
我会的
I will.
你最好找到鲍尔并让一切回归正轨 托尼
You'd better find Bauer and make this thing work, Tony.
不然你们和那个不知死活杰克
Otherwise, the two of you and Jack, assuming he's still alive,
将为今天所发生的一切负责
are going to take the fall for everything that happened today,
包括监狱暴动 萨拉扎的越狱还有因此导致的牺牲者
from the prison riots to Salazar's escape and every dead body in between.
如果杰克去交易却得不到支援会怎么样?
So, what happens if Jack goes to this meeting without backup?
萨拉扎会拿到病毒
The Salazars get the virus.
之后会怎么样?
What happens from there?
我也没头绪
I don't know.
感觉好些了么?
Feeling better?
我没事了
I'm fine.
阿马多尔
Amador.
喂 杰克
Hello, Jack.
这几位一定是你所代表的买家
So these must be the buyers you're representing.
这两位是赫克托和拉姆·萨拉扎
This is Hector and Ramon Salazar.
有1亿美金在日内瓦和香港的契约户口
There's $100 million in escrow accounts in Geneva and Hong Kong.
我们已经准备好随时转账
We're prepared to give immediate instructions to have the money transferred
只等病毒到位
as soon as we have confirmation that the virus has been delivered.
情况变复杂了
There's been a complication.
另一个买家也想要病毒
Another buyer's interested in the virus.
你在说什么? 我们已经谈定了
What are you talking about? We have a deal.
-这怎么回事 杰克?  -我不知道
-What's going on, Jack?  -I don't know.
杰克和此事无关
Jack had nothing to do with it.
这是几小时内 刚刚发生的情况
This is a new development. This just surfaced in the last few hours.
我们决定进行拍卖 病毒会给买价最高的一方
We'll hold an auction and the virus will go to the highest bidder.
赫克托!
Hector!
萨拉扎先生
Mr. Salazar,
我只是传达我客户的意愿
I merely represent the wishes of my client.
能让我们私下商量么?
May we have a moment?
当然
Of course.
赫克托 这不成问题
Hector, this does not need to be a problem.
-很成问题  -好好想想
-It's a huge problem.  -Think it through.
你再扔个四五千万进去
You have $40 to $50 million at this price tag,
依旧能坐收8亿的利润
and you're still looking at over an $800 million profit.
你说过这个病毒能卖到10亿美金
so you said you can move the virus for a billion dollars.
你是这么估计的不是么?
That was your estimate, right?
-差不多  -已经到这地步了
-Something like that.  -You've come this far.
别收手
Don't stop.
干到底
Let it play out.
另一个买家已经到了
The other buyer's here.
你认识她?
You know her?
这到底是怎么回事?
What the hell is he doing here?
这人是联邦特工
That man is a federal agent.
我们知道这个 尼娜
We know who he is, Nina.
-这没关系  -不 有关系
-Everything's fine.  -No, it's not.
他在套我们 我们得干掉他
He's setting us up. You have to kill him.
杀了他!
Kill him!
谁先开枪谁就出局 我说到做到
The first man who fires gets cut down. That's a promise.
他怎么会在这儿?
Why is he here?
他和你一样 尼娜 是买方代表
He represents a buyer, Nina, just like you.
不 他不是
No, he doesn't.
相信我 我了解他 无论他说了什么
Believe me, I know him. Whatever he's told you,
都是骗你的
he's lying.
我已经不为反恐局干了 尼娜
I don't work for CTU anymore, Nina.
我给自己干
I work for myself.
-我走了  -尼娜 拜托了
-I'm out of here.  -Nina, please.
让她走 我们继续原来的约定
Let her go and honor the original agreement.
尼娜!
Nina!
你的客户知道你这样离开
I don't think your client's going to be too happy if you walk out
让病毒落入他手后 不会高兴的
and let the virus go to another buyer.
我们得拿下这笔交易
We gotta close this deal.
我们到处都有人放风
We have a wide perimeter, lookouts everywhere,
而且也监听着每条频道
and we're monitoring every frequency.
25公里内没有任何执法机关和军队
There's no law or military within 25 kilometers.
你知道我的作风
You know how I work.
这里很安全
This area is completely secure.
如果我起疑心 那我根本不会来
If I had the slightest doubt, I wouldn't be here.
我建议大家都冷静一会
I suggest we all take a few minutes to calm ourselves.
然后我就开始解释规矩
Then I'll explain the ground rules,
让我们开始投标
and we'll proceed with the bids.
同意么?
Agreed?
行
Agreed.
好吧
Fine.
很好
Good.
大卫.
David
艾伦 很高兴见到你
Alan, it's good to see you.
谢谢你百忙之中抽空看我
Thanks for finding the time to fit me in.
你总是为我安排时间 艾伦
You've always made time for me, Alan,
即使没有要事
even when there was no obvious reason to do so.
你是很有潜力的 大卫.
Your potential was always obvious, David.
你怎么样?
How are you doing?
我身体有些部分不灵光了
Well, I could use a few new body parts,
-但除此以外  -你看起来不错
-but besides that...  -Well, you look well.
我知道你很好奇找你有什么要事
I know you're wondering what could be so important that I'd ask you here,
我直截了当地说吧
so I'll be brief and I'll be blunt.
我要你兄弟退出政权
I want your brother off the team.
我不明白 你一直很支持韦恩
I don't understand. You've always been supportive of Wayne.
曾经是
I was.
但现在不是
I'm not anymore.
这是为什么 艾伦?
What's this all about, Alan?
-老爷?  -让我妻子过来
-Yes, sir?  -Tell my wife to come in here.
马上
Right away, sir.
朱莉娅.
Julia
总统先生
Mr. President.
大卫想知道为什么我要他解雇韦恩
David is wondering why I want him to fire Wayne,
我觉得你能告诉他
and I thought you should explain.
如你所知 我和韦恩相识有一会儿了
As you know, I've known Wayne for some time.
三年前
Three years ago,
当他是艾伦公司总裁时
when he was President of Alan's company,
我们经常呆在一起
we began to spend quite a bit of time together.
说到点上 朱莉娅
Get to it, Julia.
韦恩和我坠入爱河
Wayne and I became involved.
他们发生了关系!
They had an affair,
当时我还在康复
while I was recuperating from the stroke.
你兄弟就这么报答我
That's how your brother thanked me.
继续
Go on.
在你要求他加入你政权前
We saw each other for a year,
我和他交往了一年
before you asked him to join your administration.
然后我们就分手了
Then we broke it off.
等等
Hold on.
如果你知道这事 为什么当时你不表态?
If you knew about this, why didn't you say something?
我不知道
I didn't.
是最近刚发现的
I just found out recently.
你知道么 大卫?
Did you know, David?
-你也瞒着我么?  -当然没有
-Did you keep it from me, too?  -Of course not.
我甚至无法相信这是真的
I can hardly even believe it's true.
是真的
It's true.
-我告诉过你 我有多抱歉  -你出去
-I've told you how sorry I am.  -You can go.
我一直等你来洛杉矶 这样我能亲自找你
I waited for you to come to Los Angeles so I could do this face-to-face.
我把公司交给你兄弟
I gave your brother my company,
而他拐走了我妻子
and he took my wife.
现在我要夺走他的工作
Now I'm taking away his job.
韦恩是我的总管
Wayne is my chief of staff,
我最好的朋友
my closest friend.
-我信任他  -我不信任
-I trust him.  -I don't,
你也不应该 他不正直
and neither should you. He's dishonest.
我以为你会赞同我 大卫
I think you would agree, David,
这些年 没有我的支持你走不到这一步
that you wouldn't be where you are without my support over the years.
我从来不求回报
I've never asked you for anything in return,
除了现在 我要求
but I'm asking you now.
解雇韦恩
Fire Wayne.
我很抱歉 艾伦 我做不到
I'm sorry, Alan, I can't do that.
我很失望...
I'm disappointed...
... 但并不惊讶
... but not surprised.
你也了解我 知道这样做会有什么结果
And you know me well enough not to be surprised if there are repercussions.
我希望你这不是在威胁我
I hope you're not threatening me.
我从不威胁人 大卫
I don't make threats, David.
我说到做到
I just tell it like it is.
如果你改变了主意 记得联系我
You let me know if you change your mind.
让他们调查这些位置
Have them open up the field search to these coordinates...
告诉他们这优先处理
tell them it's a priority.
-你要我找...  -抱歉 我并不想打岔
-Do you want me to ask...  -Sorry, I don't mean to interrupt,
能和你私下谈谈么?
but can I see you for a minute?
你这些活够么?
Do you have enough to go on?
如果联系卫星处有问题 我会找你
I'll let you know if the satellite guys give me any trouble.
怎么了?
What is it?
是托尼的事
It's actually about Tony.
听我说...
Look...
我不知道...
I don't know if he's...
你不知道...
You don't know if he...
什么?
what?
我不知道他到底干得了干不了
I don't know if he's well enough to do his job.
金 几小时前他刚中弹
Kim, he was shot a few hours ago.
他没法全力工作
He's not going to be working at full capacity.
我知道 但是如果他总是漏掉关键怎么办?
I know, but what if he misses something important?
我指如果他搞砸了事
I mean, he's running things.
出了什么事?
What happened?
他让我完成通讯文件
He asked me to finalize the comm files,
但是他忘记给我格式码
but he forgot to give me the format codes.
至前他还骂我一顿
And then just before, he chewed me out
骂我不记得他说的事
for forgetting something he thought he told me...
但他确实没有说过
except he never told me.
他压力很大 我们也是
He's under a lot of stress... we all are.
我就是说这个
That's my point.
米歇尔 你是他老婆
Michelle, you're his wife,
你也是这里的二把手
but you're also second in command,
如果托尼干不下去
and if Tony can't do the job,
得有人转告查佩尔 而此人非你莫属
somebody has to tell Chappelle, and I think that someone should be you.
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
休息一会
Taking a rest.
赫克托的卡车下面漏油了
There's oil under Hector's truck.
得在他回来至前修好
It needs to be fixed before Hector gets back.
快!
Now!
好吧 我会去修的
Okay, I'll check it out.
我有杰克的消息
Here, I have a message from Jack.
你能听见么?
Can you hear me?
情况和你所见不同
Things aren't what they seem.
杰克并不是拉姆和赫克托一伙的
Jack isn't really with Ramon and Hector.
他所做的一切是为了争取他们的信任
Everything he's done has been to earn their trust.
杰克想夺走他们要买的病毒
The virus that they're going to buy, Jack is going to take it from them.
你明白么?
Do you understand?
你们国家的士兵离这儿不远
There are soldiers from your country not far from here.
只要杰克一给信号他们就来
They'll come when Jack calls for them.
克劳迪娅?
Claudia?
杰克保证如果我帮你 就带着我全家离开
Jack promised to get me and my family out of here if I help you.
那就帮我
Then help me.
现在不行 周围人太多了
I can't now... there are too many men around.
但挺住
But don't give up.
我会想办法的
I'll figure out a way,
好么?
all right?
各组都会写下决定的最终要价
Each party will make one final bid in writing.
10分钟内 我们就得开始
I want all this to start in the next ten minutes.
你们得开个价
You have to come up with a number.
我们给了1个亿
We are offering a hundred.
她出价一定高很多
She must've made it enough to make this worthwhile.
大概比我们高5千万
Say, another 50.
-那么我们给1亿7千5百万?  -不够
-So we go 175?  -More.
如果我们要干 就得狠下心
If we do this, we do it to win.
至少2个亿
At least 200.
去联系吧
Make the calls.
她是谁?
Who is she?
我说过了 她以前在反恐局是我的搭档
I told you, she was my partner at CTU.
不对
No.
你们之间的关系不只如此
There's more between you and this woman.
她杀了我妻子
She killed my wife.
这会影响你么 杰克?
Is this going to be a problem, Jack?
不
No.
不会
No problem.
-我们去哪儿?  -我们一起走
-Where are we going?  -We'll be together.
我们现在也在一起
We're together now.
赫克托会和我们一起来么?
Is Hector coming with us?
塞尔吉奥 只管做准备离开
Sergio, just be ready to leave.
-但是赫克托呢?  -塞尔希 忘掉他!
-But what about Hector?  -Sergio, forget about Hector!
只管按我说的做!
Just do what I'm telling you!
你要做什么?
What are you about to do?
杰克说如果我救他搭档 他就帮我们离开 爸爸
Jack said if I help his partner, he'll get us out of here, papa.
这些人...
These people...
拉姆 赫克托和杰克·鲍尔... 谁都不能信!
Ramon, Hector, Jack Bauer... you can't trust any of them!
杰克跟拉姆 赫克托他们不一样
Jack's not like Ramon and Hector.
爸爸 拜托了 这是我们脱离这里的机会
Papa, please, this is our chance to get out of here.
那就去吧
Then go.
不
No.
我们一起走
No, we're all going.
我不会丢下你的
No, I'm not going without you.
那么地面卫星a39呢?
What about Landsat alpha three-nine?
对 没错
Yeah, that's about it, right.
谢谢
Thanks.
我刚查了国安局的纪录
I just checked all the NSA logs.
没有任何卫星行经杰克可能所在的区域
There're no satellites going through the area we think Jack's in.
保险起见 我会检查航线
I'll check the flight paths just in case.
保险什么? 我刚查过
Just in case what? I just checked it.
这不是今天第一个问题了 托尼
There've been other mistakes today, Tony.
问题
Mistakes.
你认为是我造成的?
You think I made them?
亲爱的 你应该继续留在医院
Sweetheart, you should still be in the hospital.
如果你不是状态不是百分百好 应该退居二线
If you're not a hundred percent, you should step down.
我没事
I'm fine.
你今天遇上的一切
And after what you've been through today,
-让我不觉得...  -我说我没事
-I don't see how you...  -I just said I'm fine, all right.
到此为止
End of discussion, please.
托尼 我找到了这个
Tony, I've got something.
国安局有颗卫星能够让我们重新定位
NSA's got a satellite we may be able to reposition.
我们只需要许可
We just have to ask for access.
-好的 谢谢  -没事
-All right, thanks.  -Yeah.
怎么?
Yes?
我要和你谈谈 瑞恩
I need to talk to you, Ryan.
等下
Hold on.
我觉得托尼现在不应该呆在这儿
I don't think Tony should be here right now.
据我所知 他并没有受任何重伤
My understanding is, he's not in any imminent danger.
不 不是指这个
No, it's not that.
我收到报告 他一直健忘
I've had reports he's been forgetful,
漏掉信息
missing things.
-比方说?  -关键信息
-Like what?  -Key information.
格式码 某些会造成拖延的事情
Format codes. Things that are causing delays.
平日里我不会担心这个 但是...
On any other day, I wouldn't be worried about this, but...
我不知道他今天到底行不行
I'm just not sure if he's up to it today.
如果我现在把他停职 我们的进度也会慢
If I pull him now, that sets us back, too.
没人能替代他
No one can replace what he does.
他 盖尔还有杰克是此次计划的始作俑者
He, Gael and Jack have been working this from the beginning.
除非你认为他犯的错误很严重...
Unless you think his mistakes are significant enough...
对
I do.
不然我不会来找你
Or else I wouldn't be bringing this to you.
好吧
All right.
让我处理完这个电话 就着手解决
Just let me wrap up this call and I'll get into it.
谢谢
Thank you.
我明白 但是你得办到
I understand that, but you need to make it happen.
我刚从艾伦那边回来
I just got back from seeing Alan.
他有什么事?
What did he want?
我想你心里明白
Oh, I think you know.
明白什么 大卫?
Know what, David?
他要我解雇你!
He wants me to fire you!
你到底在想什么
What the hell were you thinking,
和有夫之妇发生关系?!
carrying on an affair with a married woman?!
她老公还是我最大的支持者!
The wife of my biggest supporter!
听着 我很抱歉
Listen, I am sorry.
但是这个错误 我已经更正了
But it was a mistake, and I corrected it.
艾伦不这么想
Not in Alan's mind.
对他来说 这是刚发生的
For him, this is fresh.
他刚刚得知
He just found out,
而且他要你付出代价
and he wants to make you pay.
听着 我们都知道你不能和艾伦作对
Look, we both know you can't afford to make an enemy out of Alan.
他权势太大
He wields too much power.
所以...
So...
我会辞职
I'll resign.
你的去留 是由我决定而不是艾伦·米利肯
You'll leave only I decide it's the right thing to do, not Alan Milliken.
大卫 相信我 艾伦是个心狠手辣的人
David, Alan is a very dirty fighter, trust me.
你真的要和他作对?
Are you sure you want to get down in the gutter with that man?
你逼得我别无选择 不是么?
Well, you haven't left me much choice, have you?
你找我 瑞恩?
You wanted to see me, Ryan?
对
Yeah.
怎么了?
What's going on?
我找你 因为有人质疑你的能力
I asked you here because your competency has been brought into question.
谁?
By whom?
我
By me.
一位职员告诉我...
An employee came to me with some concerns, and I...
-一位职员?  -金 鲍尔
-An employee?  -Kim Bauer.
而我觉得有必要说明你的状况
And I felt I needed to address them.
和瑞恩?
With Ryan?
你不先来找我?
You didn't come to me first?
-我找过你了 托尼 你不肯...  -够了
-tried to talk to you, Tony, you wouldn't...  -Enough.
事实上 瑞恩 他们错了
The point is, Ryan, is that they're wrong.
我完全胜任我的工作
I am fit for duty completely.
好吧 你进来的时候
Alright, when you entered the room,
显示器是开着的
the monitor was on.
告诉我 上面有些什么
Tell me what it showed.
左半边是美国的电脑合成图像
On the left side was a c-tan schematic of the country,
标明在佛罗里达 纽约和蒙大拿
indicating an ongoing investigation in Florida,
进行的调查
New York and Montana.
右半边是奥斯汀银行的报告
On the right side was an all clear report from the Austin branch.
没错
That's correct.
但是这并不能解释你所犯的纰漏
But it still doesn't ease my mind considering the slips you made.
什么纰漏?
What slips?
米歇尔?
Michelle?
你认为你把频率扫描的识别给了金
You thought you gave Kim the signature on the frequency scans.
但你没给
You didn't.
并没有口头给
Not verbally, no.
我和她谈话15分钟之前 我发到了她的屏幕上
I put them on her "inscreen" 15 minutes before I talked to her.
还有什么?
Anything else?
他说你没有及时地把格式码发到她的表格里
She said you didn't load the format codes onto the grid in time.
不 我并没有给她发过去
No. I didn't load the format codes onto her grid.
我把格式码及时地发到了共享硬盘里
I put them in the shared volume on time.
自己查
Check it.
在那儿
It's there.
好吧 很抱歉 托尼
All right, I'm sorry, Tony.
我们谈完了
We're done here.
很好
Good.
你浪费了我们重要的时间
You've wasted time we don't have.
你们想好开价了么?
Are you ready with your bids?
-是的  -是的
-Yes.  -Yes.
让我们看看
Let me see them.
银行会确认这些资金?
And the banks will verify the presence of these funds?
没错
Yes, that is correct.
银行也会确认这些资金的
The bank will verify those as well.
你们开价2亿2千5百万
Your bid is $225 million.
她的是2亿4千万
Hers is 240.
尼娜,
Nina
你赢了
you win.
你死定了
You are a dead man.
我的人会带你们出去
My people will escort you out.
2小时内交易
The transfer will take place in two hours.
你说会把病毒带来 你失败了!
You said you were going to deliver the virus, you failed!
还没结束呢 赫克托
Not now, Hector.
走吧
Come on.
我会通知你细节
I'll be contacting you with the details.
很好
Excellent.
-我们会等你电话  -走吧
-We'll be waiting for your call.  -Let's go!
你不能眼睁睁的看着尼娜·迈尔斯这样离开
You can't let Nina Myers just walk away from it.
-你得派人跟着她  -闭嘴!
-You got to put a man on her.  -Shut up!
拉姆 听我说
Ramon, listen to me.
尼娜现在一走
Nina gets away now,
就会无影无踪 你永远也找不到她
she'll disappear. You'll never find her again.
你已经有过机会了 杰克
You had your chance, Jack.
好了
All right.
这儿就行了
This is good enough.
拉姆 求你了 你这是酿成大错
Ramon, please. You're making a mistake.
-出去  -我能解释 我不知道...
-Get out.  -I can explain. I didn't know...
出去!
Get out!
你对我们已经没有利用价值了
You're of no use to us anymore.
你失败了!
You failed!
赫克托 别这么做!
Hector, don't do this!
拉姆 好好想想
Ramon, think this through.
那些你承诺过会提供病毒的买家怎么办?
What about all your buyers around the world that you promised the virus to?
他们会发现你们被放了鸽子
They're going to know you were double-crossed
却束手无策
and that you did nothing about it.
你怎么和他们解释?
What are you going to say to them?
"对不起 我们下次会搞定的?"
"I'm sorry, we'll try and get it right next time?"
萨拉扎会被世人耻笑
The Salazar name will be a joke.
想想吧!
Come on!
5小时前 你还被关在美国监狱
Five hours ago, you were in an American prison,
你之所以能自由是因为我把你救了出来!
and now you're free because I broke you out!
而且我带给了你一笔千载难逢的生意
And then I brought you the deal of a lifetime.
你到底还要我怎么样才能证明我和你是一伙的?
What do I have to do to prove to you I'm on your side?
这桩生意还有机会
This deal can still happen.
-我们还能弄到病毒  -怎么弄?
-We can get the virus.  -How do you get the virus?
我告诉过你
I told you...
-那个女的 尼娜  -是那女的带来的问题
-the woman, Nina.  -The woman? She's the problem.
-她开价比我们高  -我认识她
-She outbid us.  -I know her.
是我训练她的
I trained her. I can get to her.
你甚至不知道哪里能找到她!
You don't even know how to find her!
我会找到的!
I'll find her!
求你了 拉姆 你不能半途而废
Please, Ramon, you can't lose here.
如果我失败了 你要杀我 可以
If I fail, you get to kill me, fine.
但是如果我成功了 那么这宗生意就能继续
But if I succeed, the deal will go forward,
一切会步入正轨 我们都能分到钱
we'll be back on track. We'll all get paid.
求你了
Please.
赫克托.
Hector
让我们再看看情况吧
Let's play this out a little longer.
这个家伙命够大
The man has more lives than a cat.